Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1890-2012; 72.1 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 29 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 152 flat boxes
  - Subseries I.K: Retail and Service Workers, 1891-2010; 24.25 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 18 manuscript boxes, and 43 flat boxes
    - Forefront: Local 342-50: United Food and Commercial Workers International Union, Mineola, NY, 1972-1976; cuid11098 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Local 37 News: Local 37, Bakery, Confectionery Workers International Union of America, Los Angeles, CA, 1963, 1974; cuid11099 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Welfare Spotlight: Local 371, SCME, AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 1958; cuid11100 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - City Hospital Worker: The Voice of Local 420, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), AFL-CIO: Local 420, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 1981, 1985-1986, 1990-1991, 1993, 1996; cuid11101 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Voice of the Cooks: Local 44, San Francisco, CA, 1951; cuid11102 (Box 59, Folder 60)
    - Garment Worker: Locals 108, 196 and 197, Northeast Dept., International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, AFL-CIO, Harrisburg, Pa, 1963-1975; cuid11103 (Box 71, Folder 7-10)
    - Notes from CNOT: Massachusetts Coalition on New Office Technology, Boston, MA, 1997 (Box 180, Folder 19, Box 184, Folder 5, Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Clean Sweep: Members of Local 74, SEIU, Bronx, NY, 1988; cuid11104 (Box 59, Folder 61)
    - L'Aiguilleur: la voix de l'ACWA: Montreal Joint Board of the ACWA, Montreal, Canada, 1952-1958, 1960; cuid10071 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Bakery Workers Organize!: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Food Industry Committee, New York, NY, 1977 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - El Combate: The Fighting Garment Worker: N.Y.-N.J. United Workers Organization Garment Committee, 1974-1976, undated; cuid11105 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Vital Signs: National Black Women's Health Project, Atlanta, GA, 1990; cuid11106 (Box 59, Folder 62)
    - Newsletter of the National Federation of Housestaff Organization: National Federation of Housestaff Organization, New York, N.Y., 1986-1988; cuid11107 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Housestaff Voice: National Federation of Housestaff Organizations, New York, NY, 1989-1992; cuid11108 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Front Lines/Premieres Lignes: National Federation of Nurses' Union, Ontario, Canada, 1989; cuid11109 (Box 59, Folder 63)
    - 1199 SEIU News: National Health and Human Service Employees Union, SEIU, AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 1986; cuid11110 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Unifier: National Rank-and-File Against Concessions, St. Paul, MN, 1985; cuid11111 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Progressive Textile Worker: National Textile Workers Progressive Committee, New York, NY, 1927; cuid11112 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - National Textile Worker: National Textile Workers Union, Olneyville, RI, 1923; cuid11113 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Life in the Factory: New England Free Press, Boston, MA, circa 1940s; cuid11114 (Box 59, Folder 64)
    - Transfusion: A Hospital Workers Newsletter: New England Free Press, Somerville, MA, 1973; cuid11115 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - USA - The Labor Revolt: New England Free Press, Boston, MA, 1967; cuid11116 (Box 59, Folder 65)
    - Keeping New York in Fashion for 10 Years: New York City Garment Industry Development Corporation, New York, NY, 1994; cuid11117 (Box 59, Folder 66)
    - We Urge: New York County Committee - American Labor Party - Garment Workers Center, New York, NY, circa 1950s; cuid11118 (Box 59, Folder 67)
    - Restaurant Employee: New York Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Local 1, New York, NY, 1977-1979; cuid11119 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Hotel Voice: New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council, AFL-CIO and Local 6, Hotel, Restaurant, Club Employees and Bartenders Union, New York, NY, 1987-1992 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Health Security by Union Action: A Report on the Sidney Hillman Center of New York: New York Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1952; cuid11120 (Box 59, Folder 68)
    - WLA Newsletter: New York/New Jersey White Lung Association, Newark, NJ, 1988; cuid11121 (Box 59, Folder 69)
    - Our Life and Times: New York's Health & Human Services Union, SEIU, AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 2010; cuid11122 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - NEWSLine for Pharmacists: NEWSLine for Pharmacists, King of Prussia, PA, 1995; cuid11123 (Box 59, Folder 70)
    - Nurses' Network: Nurses' Network, New York, NY, circa 1980s; cuid11124 (Box 59, Folder 71)
    - Local 99 News: Office & Distribution Employees' Union, Local 99, ILGWU, NY, 1986, 1991-1995; cuid11125 (Box 59, Folder 72)
    - 9 to 5: Organization for Women Office Workers, Boston, MA, 1974; cuid11126 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - 9 to 5 Newsline: Organization for Women Office Workers, Cleveland, OH, 1990-1992; cuid11127 (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - Pattern Makers' and Allied Crafts Journal: Pattern Makers League of North America, Moline, IL, 1988; cuid11128 (Box 172, Folder 40)
    - Amalgamated Bulletin: Philadelphia Joint Board, ACWA, Philadelphia, PA, 1946; cuid11129 (Box 59, Folder 73)
    - Proceedings of the Third and Fourth Constitutional Conventions of the Playthings, Jewelry & Novelty Workers International Union - CIO: Playthings, Jewelry & Novelty Workers International Union, CIO, Atlantic City, NJ, 1944 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Provision Salesmen and Distributors Union: Provision Salesmen and Distributors Union, Local 627 of New York & New Jersey, AMC & BW of NA, AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - On the Truck: Provisional Salesmen and Distributors Union, Local 627, AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 1977; cuid11130 (Box 59, Folder 74)
    - Rank and File Newsletter: Rank & File of Local 905, Bronx, NY, 1965, 1967-1968; cuid11131 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Milliner: Rank and File Committee, New York, NY, 1947-1955; cuid11132 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - 340 Leader: Retail Clothing Salesmen's Union, Local 340 ACTWU, New York, NY, 1974-1978 (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - RWDSU Record: Retail, Wholesale & Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings of the Tenth Convention of the RWDSU, AFL-CIO, CLC: Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, Miami Beach, FL, 1966 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Local 338 News: Retail Wholesale & Chain Store Food Employees Union (RWDSU/UFCW), New York, NY, 2001; cuid11133 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - 338 News: Retail, Wholesale, Chain Store Food Employee Union, New York, NY, 1941, 1971-1989; cuid11134 (Box 72, Folder 8-10)
    - Temperatures Rising: S.I. Hospital Rank & File, 1974, undated; cuid11135 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Chicanos Strike at Farah: San Francisco Bay Area Farah Strike Support Committee, San Francisco, CA, 1974; cuid11136 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Alaskero News: Seafood Processors Union, Region 37 of the Inlandboatmen's Union of the Pacific, Seattle, WA, 1995; cuid11137 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - "How to Conduct a Successful Strike": SEIU, Washington, DC, circa 1970s; cuid11138 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Clerical Update: SEIU, Clerical Division, AFL-CIO, CLC, Washington, DC, 1988; cuid11139 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - SEIU Local 535 Dragon: SEIU Local 535, Oakland, CA, 1997 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - Social Service Employees Union Local 371, AFSCME Proposed Merger Agreement: SSEU-AFSCME, New York, NY, Undated (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Service Employee: Service Employee International Union, Washington, DC, 1971-1987; cuid11140 (Box 97, Folder 1-7, Box 98, Folder 1-5, Box 99, Folder 1-3)
    - Special Bulletin: Service Employees International Union, Local 32-J, New York, NY, 1969; cuid11141 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - United Worker: Service Employees Union, San Francisco, CA, 1996; cuid11142 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - T&G Workplace Record: T&G Research, England, 1997-1998; cuid11143 (Box 172, Folder 36)
    - T.W.O.C. Parade: Textile Workers Organizing Committee, Atlanta, GA, 1937; cuid11144 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Joint Board: Textile Workers Organizing Committee of the C.I.O., Holyoke, MA, 1937; cuid11145 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Bulletin of the John R. Commons Labor Reference Center: Textile Workers Union of America Papers, Wisconsin, Undated (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the Biennial Convention of the Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, CLC: Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, CLC, Miami Beach, FL, 1946-1966 (Box 187, Folder 4-5)
    - Executive Council Report of the Seventh Biennial Convention of the Textile Workers Union of America: Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, Cleveland, OH, 1952 (Box 180, Folder 9, Box 186, Folder 5)
    - FDR fundraising circular: Textile Workers Union of America, 1944; cuid11146 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - International Labor Standards - A Key to World Security: Textile Workers Union of America, New York, NY, 1940s; cuid11147 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Union in Wartime Pamphlet: Textile Workers Union of America, New York, NY, circa 1940s; cuid11148 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Activities Bulletin: Textile Workers Union of America Educational Department, New York, NY, circa 1930s; cuid11149 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Amalgamated Banks: A Report on the Realization of a Dream, Biennial Report 1954-1955: The Amalgamated Banks/Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Amalgamated Health Centers: A Report on the Realization of a Dream, Biennial Report 1954-1955: The Amalgamated Health Centers/Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Layoff Revue: The Anti-Imperialist Collective, Cambridge, MA, 1972; cuid11150 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Baker's Journal: The Bakery and Confectionary Workers' International Union of America, Chicago, IL, 1916; cuid11151 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Get Organized!: Toyworkers for Democracy Local 223, Newark, NJ, 1978-1980; cuid11152 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - The Textile Worker: Transport and General Workers Union Dryers Bleachers and Textile Workers Trade Group, Bradford, UK, 1984; cuid11153 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Textile Labor: TWUA, Roanoke Rapids, NC, 1975; cuid11154 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - USA Record: Uniformed Sanitationmen's Association, New York, NY, 1966-1967; cuid11155 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - USDAW Today: Union of Shop, Distributive and Allied Workers, England, 1990-1997; cuid11156 (Box 66, Folder 3-6, Box 89, Folder 1-3)
    - 65 Store Worker: United Department Store Workers Union, District 65 RWDSU, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - UFCW Action: United Food and Commercial Workers Union, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Local 888 Your News: United Food & Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Mount Vernon, NY, 1995; cuid11157 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Local 881 Stewards' Advocate: United Food and Commercial Workers International Union Local 881, Oak Brook, IL, 1995; cuid11158 (Box 172, Folder 38)
    - Local 342-50 Forefront: United Food and Commercial Workers Union, Mineola, NY, 1984-2001; cuid11159 (Box 88, Folder 4-5)
    - UFCW Local 174 News: United Food and Commercial Workers Union, New York, NY, 1991; cuid11160 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Action against Jim Crow: United Packinghouse Workers of America, circa 1950s; cuid11161 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - UPWA Champion: United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1956; cuid11162 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - URW: The United Rubber Worker: United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, CLC, Akron, OH, 1989; cuid11163 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Building a union of textile workers: United Textile Workers of America, 1939; cuid11164 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Textile Challenger: United Textile Workers of America, Lawrence, NY, 1978-1995; cuid11165 (Box 90, Folder 1-7)
    - New Voices: United Wholesale and Warehouse Employees of New York, New York, NY, 1938; cuid11166 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - UIU Journal: Upholsterers' International Union of North America, Philadelphia, Pa, 1978-1985; cuid11167 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the Biennial Convention of the Textile Workers Union of America: Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union Local 65-CIO, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 200, Folder 11, Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Darbas, 1966; cuid11168 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - de Klerenkrant, 1990; cuid11169 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Hospital Worker: Rank and File Paper run by hospital workers, London, England, 1973, 1977; cuid11170 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Hotel Worker, 1937; cuid11171 (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Office Worker, 1935; cuid11172 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Paperworker, 1990-1996; cuid11173 (Box 91, Folder 1-4, Box 92, Folder 1-3)
    - Three Years Later - The Uprising of '34, 1998; cuid11174 (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Women's Occupational Health Resource Center News, 1979; cuid11175 (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - 1199 SEIU News: 1199 SEIU, New York, NY, 2000-2004 (Box 230, Folder 16-19)
    - Local 814 News: 814 Members' Committee to Elect Paul Poulos, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 183, Folder 13)
  - Subseries I.L: Transportation Workers, 1892-2012; 17.7 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 18 manuscript boxes, and 26 flat boxes
    This series contains publications issued by national and local unions of transit workers, including a significant number of titles issued by Teamster organizations, encompassing local and rank and file chapters of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters and Teamsters for a Democratic Union. Several other national unions -- Retail, Wholesale & Department Store Union; Transport Workers Union of America; United Auto Workers -- are represented, often by subsidiary groups like Auto Workers United to Fight.
    - Contact: Air Transport Local 501, TWU-CIO, Jackson Heights, NY, 1946-1948; cuid11176 (Box 73, Folder 33)
    - Wing Ways: Air Transport Local 501, TWU-CIO, LaGuardia Field, NY, 1947-1948; cuid11177 (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - Airliner: Airline Employees' Local 508, TWU-CIO, LaGuardia Field, NY, 1947; cuid11178 (Box 73, Folder 35)
    - Union Leader: Amalgamated Association of Street Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees, Chicago, IL, 1951 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - 726 Express: Amalgamated Transit Union - Division 726, Staten Island, NY, 1990-1991, 1994; cuid11179 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Rank-N-File: Amalgamated UAW Local 893, Marshalltown, IA, 1993; cuid11180 (Box 73, Folder 36)
    - Taxi News: Arthur T. Gore, New York, NY, 1967-1977; cuid11181 (Box 114, Folder 1-7, Box 115, Folder 1-9)
    - Transit Express: ATU, Staten Island, NY, 1988-1990; cuid11182 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - 76 Auto Contracts - A Time to Fight!: Auto Workers United to Fight (UAW), Detroit, MI, 1976; cuid11183 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Auto Workers United to Fight National Newsletter: Auto Workers United to Fight (UAW), Detroit, MI, 1977-1978; cuid11184 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - National Newsletter: Auto Workers United to Fight (UAW), Detroit, MI, 1977; cuid11185 (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - Local Newsletter: Auto Workers United to Fight in '76, Elizabeth, NJ, 1976; cuid11186 (Box 172, Folder 53)
    - New York Motorist: Automobile Club of New York, 1982; cuid11187 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Fifth Wheel: Bay Area Teamster United Rank and File, Oakland, CA, 1971-1979; cuid11188 (Box 116, Folder 8, Folder 11)
    - Wildcat Dodge Truck June 1974: Black & Red, Detroit, MI, cuid11189 (Box 73, Folder 38)
    - Eight Ball: Borders Group, Inc. Union, Philadelphia, PA, circa 1990s; cuid11190 (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - New Millennium News: Borders WTC Union, New York, NY, 1997; cuid11191 (Box 73, Folder 40)
    - Hub: Boston TDU, Cambridge, MA, 1979; cuid11192 (Box 73, Folder 41)
    - Journal of Proceedings: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen, Cincinnati, OH, 1892-1896 (Box 185, Folder 6, Box 190, Folder 1, Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, San Francisco, CA, 1947-1959 (Box 208, Folder 1-2)
    - Report of Grand Lodge Officers of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Houston, TX, 1968 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Grand Lodge Proceedings: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Engineers, Des Moines, IA, 1900 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - BMWE Journal / The Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees: Brotherhood of Maintenance Way Employees, Detroit, MI, 1996-2005; cuid11193 (Box 117, Folder 1-3)
    - Railroad Trainman: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Mount Morris, IL, 1935, 1942; cuid11194 (Box 73, Folder 42)
    - Trainman News: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, IN, 1942; cuid11195 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Railway Carmen's Journal: Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada, Kansas City, MO, 1969; cuid11196 (Box 73, Folder 43)
    - Ohio Teamster: Brotherhood of Teamsters, Cleveland, OH, 1978; cuid11197 (Box 73, Folder 44)
    - Disconnected Table: Cambridge Taxi Drivers & Garage Workers, Cambridge, MA, 1973; cuid11198 (Box 73, Folder 45)
    - The Facts of the Tramways Case: Canadian Brotherhood of Railway Employees and Other Transport Workers, Ottawa, Canada, 1944; cuid11199 (Box 73, Folder 46)
    - Lemon Times: Center for Auto Safety, Washington, DC, 1986-1994; cuid11200 (Box 73, Folder 47)
    - Chicago Area PROD Newsletter: Chicago Area PROD, Westmont, IL, 1981; cuid11201 (Box 73, Folder 48)
    - Clerical News - B.O.T.-Construction & Operation: Clerical Section 211 of the Transport Workers Union, New York, NY, 1938, undated; cuid11202 (Box 73, Folder 49)
    - Contract Countdown: Coalition for a Good Contract, UAW, Detroit, MI, 1976; cuid11203 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Teamster Talk: Colorado Teamsters for a Democratic Union, Denver, CO, 1980; cuid11204 (Box 73, Folder 50)
    - Transport Workers Bulletin: Committee for the Organization of a Transport Workers Union, New York, NY, 1933; cuid11205 (Box 73, Folder 89, Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Union Drivers and Mechanics Say No! to Bus Cuts & Fare Raises: Committee of Concerned MTA Mechanics, circa 1990s; cuid11206 (Box 73, Folder 51)
    - Speaking Out: Communications Workers of America, Local 3601, Detroit, MI, 1986; cuid11207 (Box 123, Folder 102)
    - C.A.M.: Concerned Autoworkers Movement, Fremont, CA, 1979; cuid11208 (Box 73, Folder 52)
    - Draggin' the Line: Concerned Drivers, San Francisco, CA, 1974 (Box 213, Folder 24)
    - Rank and File Advocate: Concerned Members of New Directions/TWU 100, Bronx, NY, 2001-2005; cuid11209 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - From the Horse's Mouth: Concerned Rank and File Teamsters (CRAFT), Pittsburgh, Pa, 1975, 1979-1981; cuid11210 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Grapevine: Concerned Truckers for a Democratic Union, Chicago, IL, 1975-1976; cuid11211 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Taxi Union News: Democratic Union Organizing Committee Local 777, Chicago, IL, 1966-1968; cuid11212 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - 1250 News: Department Store Employees Union, New York, NY, 1938-1939; cuid11213 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Unity News: Department Store Workers Committee For Unity, New York, NY, 1953; cuid11214 (Box 73, Folder 53)
    - Teamsters Rank and File Speaks: Detroit Metro TDU, Detroit, MI, 1982; cuid11215 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - RPM: Detroit Organizing Committee, Detroit, MI, 1970-1972; cuid11216 (Box 118, Folder 3-4)
    - Federated Railwayman: Division No. 4, Railway Employees' Department, Montreal, Canada, 1953; cuid11217 (Box 73, Folder 54)
    - Durham Express: Durham Unity Team, Washington, DC, 1991; cuid11218 (Box 73, Folder 55)
    - Rank & File Reformer: Eastern PA. T.D.U., Analomink, PA, 1979; cuid11219 (Box 73, Folder 56)
    - UAW Ammunition: Education Department, International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Detroit, MI, 1971; cuid11220 (Box 73, Folder 57)
    - UAW-CIO Ammunition: Education Department, International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW-CIO), Indianapolis, IN, 1954 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - 719 News: Electro-Motive Diesel Workers Union - Local 719 UAW, Brookfield, IL, 1948; cuid11221 (Box 73, Folder 58)
    - Voice of Local 259: Executive Board of Local 259, 1947, 1949, 1954; cuid11222 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Federation News: Federation of Public Employees/Transport Workers Union, AFL-CIO, San Francisco, CA, 1970, 1972; cuid11223 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Surface Wheels: Flatbush Wheels, Brooklyn, NY, Undated (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Ford World: Ford Motor Company, Employee Communication Department, Dearborn, MI, 1980; cuid11224 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Transport: Fraternite Canadienne des Employes de Chemins de fer et Autres Transports, Montreal, Canada, 1952; cuid11225 (Box 73, Folder 59)
    - Taxi News Transport: Fred Swartz, New York, NY, 1963-1966; cuid11226 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Teamster Pride: General Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers of Local 886, Oklahoma City, OK, 1991; cuid11227 (Box 73, Folder 60)
    - Union Dues: Graduate Employee Organization, 1992; cuid11228 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Hawaiian Teamster Organizer: Hawaii Teamsters & Allied Workers Union, 1977; cuid11229 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Local 707 News: Highway and Local Motor Freight Drivers, Dockmen and Helpers Local Union No. 707, Woodside, NY, 1980; cuid11230 (Box 73, Folder 61)
    - Workers' Unity: Hydramatic Chapter of Autoworkers United to Fight in '76, 1976-1977; cuid11231 (Box 73, Folder 62, Box 189, Folder 14)
    - IDA News: Independent Drivers Association, Denver, CO, 1975; cuid11232 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Skilled Tradesman: Independent Skilled Trades Council (UAW), Detroit, MI, 1975, 1978-1980, undated; cuid11233 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - ITOC News: Independent Taxi Owners Council, Inc./Hosynd Publications, Inc., Glen Cove, NY, 1976, 1984; cuid11234 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Interborough Bulletin: Interborough Rapid Transit Company, New York, NY, 1935, 1937-1938; cuid11235 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - 840 News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, New York, NY, 1980-1984; cuid11236 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - IBT News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, New York, NY, 1947; cuid11237 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - News from the New Teamsters: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1996; cuid11238 (Box 73, Folder 63)
    - Teamster Leader: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1993, 1996; cuid11239 (Box 73, Folder 64)
    - Teamster News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1982; cuid11240 (Box 73, Folder 65)
    - Teamster Organizer: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1995; cuid11241 (Box 73, Folder 66)
    - Teamster UPS Update: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1995; cuid11242 (Box 73, Folder 67)
    - Teamsters Freight Bulletin: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Washington, DC, 1994-1995; cuid11243 (Box 73, Folder 68)
    - Teamsters On Parade "79" News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Tampa, FL, 1992; cuid11244 (Box 123, Folder 103)
    - Teamsters 102 News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 102, Newark, NJ, 1964-1968; cuid11245 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Local 237 Member to Member: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 237, Staten Island, NY, 1994; cuid11246 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - 237 Teamster News and Views: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 237, City Employees Union, New York, NY, 1986; cuid11247 (Box 73, Folder 69)
    - Voice of Teamsters: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 391, Greensboro, NC, 1993; cuid11248 (Box 73, Folder 70)
    - 560 Teamster Journal: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 560, Union City, NJ, 1991; cuid11249 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Reel News: International Brotherhood of Teamsters - Local 817, Lake Success, NY, 1992; cuid11250 (Box 172, Folder 44)